jaguar.com 2016-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Jaguar | Respecting website visitor privacy

Jaguar Land Rover Limited respects the privacy of every individual who visits its Web Sites and whose data it processes. Any information collected about you will be used to first fulfil any service you might request and secondly improve how as a Company we serve you. We do this by making appropriate use of the information. 

This information will not be disclosed to anyone outside of Jaguar Land Rover Limited, its affiliated or associated companies, and the dealers, agencies and licensees of any of these companies, and any other companies with which Jaguar has directly or indirectly arranged services for your benefit. It will be treated in accordance with the relevant legal provisions concerning data protection and may be initially stored and processed inside or outside the European Union anywhere in the world. It will be used only in the connection with the marketing of Jaguar products and services and related products and services. 

You have the right as an individual to find out what information we hold about you and make corrections if necessary; you also have the right to ask us to not use the information. 

We will make all practical efforts to respect your wishes. However certain legislation, especially related to safety issues or financial regulation (e.g. when dealing with Jaguar Financial Services) might prevent this. 

**JAGUAR LAND ROVER LIMITED DATA COLLECTION AND PROCESSING - - IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

Due to the international nature of Jaguar's business, Jaguar processes and stores personal data outside the EU. We are obliged to ask you to agree to this. If you do not wish to, unfortunately we will not be able to process any request you make through this website. 

If you do agree, you may do so on the basis either that we use your data ONLY to process the request you make, or that Jaguar can make further use for further contacts (always subject to the Privacy Policy below). 

**FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS (FAQ)**

1\. What are the benefits to me of Jaguar collecting my information?   
2\. What information might be collected by Jaguar Web Sites or via third party websites or platforms?   
3\. How will Jaguar collect and store this information?   
4\. For how long will Jaguar store this information?   
5\. Where will your personal information be stored?   
6\. Why do Jaguar collect this information?   
7\. Who does this policy apply to?   
8\. Jaguar's commitment to Children's Privacy.   
9\. What are cookies?   
10\. What are customer profiles?   
11\. How do I correct information about myself?   
12\. What options do I have if I choose to register?   
13\. What happens if I choose not to register? 

**WHAT ARE THE BENEFITS TO ME OF JAGUAR COLLECTING MY INFORMATION?**

Collecting this information will help Jaguar to achieve the following:   
1\. To make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.   
2\. Help us to provide information faster.   
3\. To help us create content more relevant to you.   
4\. To help you quickly find services or information available from Jaguar.   
5\. Using information to make improvements to the Site.   
6\. Assessing general trends within the Web Site and its use.   
7\. To alert you to new products, special promotions, updated information and other new services that Jaguar considers to be of interest to you. Where you have given us your permission we might authorise other companies to contact you directly.   
8\. To display relevant product, promotion and service information based on your previous browsing activities within Jaguar.com   
9\. To help you to store your favourite media (wallpapers, video, audio), configured cars and preferred dealer information within Jaguar.com for your future reference. 

**WHAT INFORMATION MIGHT BE COLLECTED BY JAGUAR WEB SITES OR VIA THIRD PARTY WEBSITES OR PLATFORMS?**

At Jaguar, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Jaguar on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect information from you on the Internet. 

Even before registration we will collect anonymous information about how you have used the Web Site. This is a common standard procedure for any Web Site on the Internet. The information collected does not personally identify you but may be helpful to us for marketing purposes or improving the services we provide. 

To improve the services we provide we will also collect anonymous information about the referring website (for example Google search) or the referring banner which lead you to Jaguar.com website. 

If you choose to give the Jaguar personal information via the Internet that we may need to correspond with you or provide you with a subscription, for example - it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. 

**HOW WILL JAGUAR COLLECT AND STORE THIS INFORMATION?**

Jaguar can collect information about you in a number of ways; either directly requesting it from you (as on a registration form) or by automatically recording information about your visit to this Site. For example we might collect data regarding your journey through the Site or record the options that you have chosen to take. Jaguar may also collect your data via third party sites or platforms such as Twitter, Jaguar will only use reputable third party platforms in order to collect your data and will ensure that it takes all practicable steps to ensure the security of your data once it has passed to us from the control of the relevant third party but the third party will be liable for the security of your data until the completion of the transfer process. 

Information is stored in a secure environment protected by a combination of physical and technical measures. There is no general public access to this information. 

Jaguar will store this information in a secure and protected environment for as long as we believe it will better help us to understand how we can serve you, and respect your wishes. 

In addition legislation might oblige us to store this information for a certain period of time. To understand how you can amend, or update information stored about you then please refer to the appropriate question in this section. 

**WHERE WILL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION BE STORED?**

Jaguar operates in many countries across the world. To enable us to offer consistent service to you, our customers, wherever you may be, we manage our Internet sites from one central site. This is currently in the United States of America. 

There is not one set of data protection law that covers both Europe and the United States of America, and the European laws require you to give your unambiguous consent to us before we can transfer and store your personal data in the United States. 

We need this information to help us improve our services to you; we want to make it easier to tailor our products and services to your particular needs. 

**WHO DOES THIS POLICY APPLY TO?**

This policy applies to web sites designed for the use of individual consumers and corporate visitors. 

**JAGUAR'S COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of children is important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13. 

**HOW DO I CORRECT INFORMATION ABOUT MYSELF?**

Some Jaguar Web Sites operate registration pages that allow you to review and update the Personal Information you have submitted. Elsewhere, you are simply given the option of cancelling your membership of the service. In other cases where you need to correct Personal Information you have submitted previously to a Jaguar Site please follow the instructions provided. 

**WHAT ABOUT INTERNET & SITE SECURITY?**

The Internet is not a secure system and you should always be cautious about the information you disclose whilst on-line. Personal Information collected by Jaguar Sites is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. In some cases, the Personal Information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction, using appropriate secure technology. 

**WHAT HAPPENS IF I CHOOSE NOT TO REGISTER?**

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you will in most cases still be able to use most of the Jaguar Web Sites. However you will not be able to access areas that require registration. Even if you do not register we will sometimes collect anonymous information about how you have used the Web Site. This is information that does not personally identify you but which may be helpful for marketing or improving the services we offer.

You are about to leave Jaguar.com. Please note that Jaguar cannot be responsible for any content or validity outside of this domain. Please click on Accept to go ahead, or on Reject to close this window.
